Saebom Pak

Front-end developer

© (236) 986-5481

github.com/saebomp

in linkedin.com/in/saebompak

Profile

A self-directed, motivated front-end developer who loves building user-friendly websites and web apps with best practices. Eager to improve development skills with a focus on clean and efficient code. Three years work experience as a UI developer in tech companies, building websites in a collaborative environment.

Skills

React / React Native / JavaScript / HTML5 / CSS / SASS / NPM / GraphQL / Github

Projects

Kovan / Team project (Front-end developer)

May 2020 - Aug 2020

Kovan is an application that manages effectively small groups.

What I did:

- Built To-do lists and polling pages with React Native.
- Implemented interactive graph chart with React Native svg.
- Applied consistent styling for expenses page.
- Built the promotional website of Kovan with React. (https://kovanapp.com/)

Result:

- Consistent styling allowed for a seamless user experience.
- Interactive graph charts have clean looking visualizations and provide a tool for users to explore data.

Smart Movie and TV Finder / Personal project

Oct 2020

A web app that lets users search for movies and TV shows. Users can browse through their favorite shows.

- Smart Movie and TV Finder provides movie and tv shows lists upon user's request.
- Upon selecting another selection from that dropdown box, the list of results refresh to reflect the updated response from the new query.
- Utilized React and Material UI.

Saebom Pak / Front-end developer

Quick Budget / Personal project

Feb 2021

A simple management app that enables users to track their expenses.

- It showcases the ability to create expenses and incomes lists and to remove them.
- Implemented the calculation functionality the total remaining budget and the total expenses and incomes.
- Visualized data with D3.js.

Work Experience

• Littlefox (Seoul, Korea) / UI Developer

Jan 2017 - Aug 2018

- Updated code to improve site performance with JavaScript, HTML 5 and CSS.
- Operated across multiple devices and browsers.
- Worked closely with design and marketing teams within an agile team environment.

Result:

This work environment allowed the development of communication and interpersonal skills. An enriched understanding of multiple devices was acquired.

• Whatever Search (Seoul, Korea) / UI Developer

Oct 2015 - Dec 2016

- Built responsive websites with HTML, CSS, JQuery and Bootstrap.
- Fixed bugs which were caused by old web browsers.
- Transitioned static websites to responsiveness.

Result:

Able to gain a greater comprehension of responsive web and cross-browsing.

Gensol Soft (Seoul, Korea) / UI Developer

Jun 2014 - Mar 2015

- Built National assembly minutes' website with Web Accessibility guidelines, HTML and CSS. (http://likms.assembly.go.kr/record/)
- Built Asian Airlines' policy manual system front-end with HTML and CSS.

Result:

Learned how to make a website accessible and became familiar with UX design while transitioning to a user-friendly website. Improved time management skills when working with clients.

Education

Langara college (Vancouver, B.C.)

Post-Degree Diploma, Web and Mobile App Design and Development / Developer stream